[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Most mornings my ___ for work at 7.30.",
			"optionA":"husband leaves",
			"optionB":"husband is leaving",
			"optionC":"leave",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I ___ for work earlier this week.",
			"optionA":"leave",
			"optionB":"am leaving",
			"optionC":"is leaving",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Steve ___ guitar for a local group. ",
			"optionA":"play",
			"optionB":"playes",
			"optionC":"plays",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Sshh, I ___ to the news.",
			"optionA":"am listening",
			"optionB":"listen",
			"optionC":"are listening",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I ___ gym whenever I get the chance.",
			"optionA":"am going to the",
			"optionB":"go to the",
			"optionC":"am go to the",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"6) I ___ a good book at the moment.",
			"optionA":"read",
			"optionB":"reads",
			"optionC":"am reading",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"My daughter ___ words to that song.",
			"optionA":"knows all the",
			"optionB":"is knowing all the",
			"optionC":"know all the",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I ___ up for school in the mornings.",
			"optionA":"hates getting",
			"optionB":"hate getting",
			"optionC":"is hating getting",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"How are you? I ___ you are well.",
			"optionA":"am hoping",
			"optionB":"hopes",
			"optionC":"hope",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I ___ in an office in London now.",
			"optionA":"am working",
			"optionB":"work",
			"optionC":"works",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I really ___ the people here.",
			"optionA":"likes",
			"optionB":"like",
			"optionC":"am liking",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Susan ___ me for lunch later.",
			"optionA":"meets",
			"optionB":"meet",
			"optionC":"is meeting",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"___ anything later?",
			"optionA":"Are you doing",
			"optionB":"Do you do",
			"optionC":"Do you doing",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I ___ my gandma next Sunday.",
			"optionA":"visit",
			"optionB":"am visiting",
			"optionC":"visiting",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	}
]